I
Move differently I think differently my belief in my ability cannot be shaken none of these guys have what I have
You know my name I'm gonna make my name I am going to break you slow
Come on, take his head, clean off.
We're not here to take part, we're here to take over.
People are always saying about the talk and I talk and I talk and I talk but guess what?
I back it up.
Thank you for watching This is the beginning of the McGregor era
I don't give a f***ing shit up.
I own this town.
I own Rio de Janeiro.
I'm sitting up here with my feet on the desk.
What's anyone up there going to do about it?
The Distances of Camera
Siegfriedia, ist unsere Macht.